qsan.com 2016-04-12

# Privacy Policy | QSAN Technology

### Privacy Policy

Qsan Technology, Inc. (“Qsan”) recognizes and respects the privacy interests of individuals with respect to information we obtain via our website. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This policy applies only to your visit to websites operated by or for Qsan. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies other than QSAN, including websites that can be linked to/from Qsan websites through banner ads or other links.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

Qsan is the sole owner of the information collected on this website. Qsan only has access to collect information that you provide to us via email or via the website. Qsan does not sell or rent this information to anyone.

Qsan will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted Qsan and to send you information about Qsan and its products and service. Qsan will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g., to ship an order. If Qsan does want to use any of the information you submit, Qsan will seek your permission.

Qsan may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website. For example, like many websites,www.Qsan.com may use “cookies”. Cookies that we generate contain no personal information about you, and we will not combine cookie information with any personal information we have collected from you via this website.

This site also logs IP addresses and Internet browser types, but we do not link such information to your personal information. Qsan never uses or shares the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via the email address or phone number given on our website.
